cityscapeglobal.com 2017-06-30

# Informa Exhibitions - Privacy Policy

This website (the “Site”) is operated by Informa Exhibitions (“we/our/us”), which is a trading division of the Informa Group.  The parent company of the Informa Group is Informa PLC.  A full list of entities within the Informa Group is available on request.

As a user of the Site (referred to as “you/your”), you acknowledge that any use of the Site is subject to this privacy policy.  We take privacy seriously and we are committed to protecting your personal information.  The purpose of this privacy policy is to set out the purposes for which, and the manner in which, we may collect and use personal information that we may obtain about you, so that you can make an informed choice about using the Site.

## **What Information Do We Collect?**

We may collect the domain name, IP address and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to the Site, the e-mail address of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit, user-specific information on what pages visitors access or visit and information volunteered by visitors, such as survey information and/or Site registrations.

When you register yourself or purchase a product/service on the Site, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, company name, address, postcode, phone number, job title, industry and other personal data (together with your credit card details when you purchase any products/services from us).  We may also ask for the contact details of other individuals within your organisation, such as your approving manager or booking contact.  If you are asked to provide details about other people, please ensure that these individuals are happy for their details to be given to us and used for the purposes set out in this privacy policy (which may include using their details for marketing purposes).

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your professional interests, experience with our products/services and more detailed contact preferences.

Where you provide us with any sensitive personal information (such as dietary or disability information) in connection with a booking for an event, we will only use this information in connection with the relevant event to serve your particular needs.  We do not retain this information in our database.

## **Use of Personal Information**

We use your personal information and other information collected from you to manage your registration, provide you with information that you request (e.g. conference papers, details of events etc.) and to improve the content of the Site and products/services you receive from us.  Your personal information may also be shared with government entities and regulatory authorities as required by law.  The use that such government entities and regulatory authorities make of your personal information is outside of our control and we do not accept any liability in this regard. 

The personal information shown or provided by you will be held on a database and, where we have appropriate authorisation, may be shared with various entities within the Informa Group, which may be based anywhere in the World.  These entities may use your information to provide you with information about Informa Group products and services which they think may be of interest to you.  For more information about the types of marketing we carry out, please see the section entitled “Direct Marketing” below.

We may employ the services of third parties to help us in certain areas, such as website hosting or marketing campaigns.  In some cases, such third parties may receive your information.  However, at all times we will control and be responsible for the use of your information.

We may use aggregated information for the purposes of tracking Site usage, in order to help improve the Site and for research and analysis purposes.  We may pass this information to third parties.  The aggregate information and statistics will not, however, include details that can be used to identify you.

Where you have given your consent, your details may be made available to carefully selected third parties such as our sponsors or partners for their own marketing purposes.

## **Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

The Site uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including cookies.  A cookie is a small text file written to a user's hard drive that contains the 'User ID'.  Cookies record those areas of the Site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long.  The use of cookies and tracking technologies is now widespread by websites in order to track traffic flows.  We use cookies and other tracking technologies to enable us to offer certain time-saving features to our users, such as one-time log in, global-site shopping cart functionality and pre-populating name and address fields.  If a user sets up their browser to reject cookies or other tracking technologies, he or she may still use the Site, although functionality will be impaired.  You can find out more about the use of cookies and how to disable/enable them on [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/).

We may combine your visitor session information or other information collected through tracking technologies with personally identifiable information in order to understand and measure your online experiences and to determine what products, promotions and services are likely to be of interest to you.

We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send to our visitors for a number of purposes, including: (i) to determine whether our visitors have opened or forwarded those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails, (ii) to customise the display of banner advertisements and other messages after a visitor has closed an e-mail, and (iii) to determine whether a visitor has made an enquiry or a purchase in response to a particular e-mail.

Cookies and other technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to a third party authorised by us to collect information on our behalf.  The information from the use of such technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

## **Log Files**

We use cookies and log files to administer the Site, track users' movements and actions and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  The information gathered can thus be used to improve the Site and the user experience.

## **Direct Marketing**

In order to provide you with a better service, Informa Exhibitions, various entities within the Informa Group and other carefully selected third parties (such as our sponsors or partners) would like to use your personal information to send you information about their products and services which they think may be of interest to you.  Where we and/or they have appropriate authorisation/consent, we/they may send you mailings by post, call you or send you e-mails, SMS' and faxes.

## **User's Right to Opt-Out**

If you do not want to receive communications from us, other entities within the Informa Group or third parties you may opt out of such communications by sending an e-mail to [gedatateam@informa.com](mailto:gedatateam@informa.com)or by calling or writing to us (our contact details are given below).

## **Period of Grace**

We will endeavour to update your records as promptly as practical.  However, you may continue to receive communications for a transitional period whilst we process your request.

## **Security**

We take reasonable precautions on the Site to protect and maintain the security of your information.  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked or open (as will be the case for most of the time that a user is browsing the web).  However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised third parties will never be able to defeat security measures or access and use your personal information for improper purposes.

## **Hyperlinks and Third Party Advertising**

The Site contains links to other websites.  Their inclusion cannot be taken to imply any endorsement or validation by us of the content of such other websites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites and nor do we accept any liability in connection with the content or otherwise of such websites.  We may display third party advertisements on the Site.  Cookies may be associated with these advertisements to enable the advertiser to track the number of anonymous users responding to the campaign.  We do not have access to or control over cookies placed by third parties.

## **Sale of the Business**

In the event that our business is sold or integrated with another business, your details will be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchaser's advisors and will be passed to the new owners of the business.

## **Changes/Updates to the Privacy Policy**

In order to keep up with changing legislation and best practice, we may revise this privacy policy at any time without notice and so please check back periodically so that you are aware of any changes.

## **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or feel that your privacy has been compromised, please contact us at:

  * Legal Department: Informa PLC, 5 Howick Place, London, SW1P 1WG, UK / +44 (0) 20 7017 5000
  * Data Team: [gedatateam@informa.com](mailto:gedatateam@informa.com)
